(Penny:)No. No woman would.
See, now, that's the great thing.
We're out as friends.
(Leonard:)This is not a date. Sex is off the table.
(Leonard:)So let's go learn
why hydroelectric power...
(Leonard:)...might not be the environmental
bargain you think it is.
(Leonard:)Sorry, spoiler alert.
- Ugh. All right. Fine.
- Thanks.
Uh, tickets are 11 bucks.
(Penny:)Not a date.
(Raj:)Come on, Sheldon. Star Wars.
I'm pushing play. I mean it.
Yeah, if we don't start soon,
George Lucas is gonna change it again.
(Sheldon:)This would go a lot faster
if you put your diploma to work...
...and help me set up this high-frequency
tone generator.
I have a master's degree from MIT.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but you've got a can-do attitude,
and that's what's important.